Exercise 3-5, reading the AH sound. Listen to the audio and then read the following
aloud. A lot of long hot walks in the garden. John was not sorry when the boss
called off the walks in the garden. Obviously to him it was awfully hot and
the walks were far too long. He had not thought that walking would have caught on
the way it did and he fought the policy from the onset. At first, he thought he
could talk it over at the law office and have it quashed, but a small obstacle
halted that thought. The top lawyers always bought coffee at the shop across
the lawn, and they didn't want stop on John's account. John's problem was not
office politics, but office policy. He resolved the problem by bombing the
garden. Read a lot of long hot walks in the garden aloud.